Guide to the Billboard Photograph Collection ca 1918-1934 PR 5
New-York Historical Society
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59796)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59797)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59798)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59799)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59800)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59801)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59802)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59803)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59804)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 6, Item 59805)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59806)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59807)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59808)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59809)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59810)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59811)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59812)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59813)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co.; view of Bryant Park, May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59814)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co.; view of Bryant Park, May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59815)
- Willis near E. 148th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59816)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59817)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59818)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59819)
- Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59820)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59821)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59822)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59823)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59824)
- 8th Ave & 110th Taken from "El," looking SW; billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., May, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59825)
- 8th Ave & 110th Taken from "El," looking SW; billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., June, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59826)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., June, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59827)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., June, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59828)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., June, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59829)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., June, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59830)
- 7th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., June, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59831)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., June, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59832)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., June, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59833)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., June, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59834)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., June, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59835)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., June, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59836)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., June, 1922 (Box 7, Item 59837)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59838)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59839)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59840)
- unspecified (Box 8, Item 59841)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59842)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59843)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59844)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59845)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59846)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59847)
- Willis near E. 148th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59848)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59849)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59850)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., February, 1923 (Box 8, Item 59851)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59852)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59853)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59854)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., 1923 (Box 8, Item 59855)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Advertising Co., October 23, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59856)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Advertising Co., 1925 (Box 8, Item 59857)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Advertising Co., April, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59858)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co.; billboards blank, April, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59859)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., April, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59860)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co. and General Outdoor Adv. Co., April, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59861)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., April, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59862)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., April, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59863)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co., April, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59864)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thos. Cusack Co. and General Outdoor Adv. Co/., April, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59865)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; view of Bryant Park, April, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59866)
- Willis near E. 148th, September, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59867)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co. and Thomas Cusack Co., September, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59868)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59869)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thomas Cusack Co., September, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59870)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thomas Cusack Co. and General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59871)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59872)
- 6th Ave & 27th, September, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59873)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., September, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59874)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; view of Bryant Park, September, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59875)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx), September, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59876)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 26, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59877)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thomas Cusack Co., August 26, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59878)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by Thomas Cusack Co. and General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 26, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59879)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by Thomas Cusack Co., August 26, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59880)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 28, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59881)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; views of Bryant Park, August 28, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59882)
- Willis near E. 148th, August 28, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59883)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx), August 28, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59884)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by Thomas Cusack Co. and General Outdoor Advertising Co., August 28, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59885)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Advertising Co. and Van Beuren Co., August 28, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59886)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Advertising Co., August 29, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59887)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thomas Cusack Co., August 29, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59888)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 29, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59889)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 29, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59890)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 29, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59891)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co. and Thos. Cusack Co., October 23, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59892)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 23, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59893)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 24, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59894)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 24, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59895)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 24, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59896)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 24, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59897)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 24, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59898)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 24, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59899)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 24, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59900)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox, October 26, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59901)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx), October 26, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59902)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Great Outdoor Adv. Co., October 26, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59903)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thos. Cusack. Co., October 26, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59904)
- Willis near E. 148th, October 26, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59905)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 23, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59906)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co. and Murphy & Brode, December 23, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59907)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 23, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59908)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 23, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59909)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 23, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59910)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co. and Thos. Cusack Co., December 23, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59911)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 23, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59912)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., December 28, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59913)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx), December 28, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59914)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by Great Outdoor Adv. Co., December 28, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59915)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Great Outdoor Adv. Co., December 28, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59916)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Great Outdoor Adv. Co., December 28, 1925 (Box 8, Item 59917)
- 6th Ave & 27th, December 28, 1925 (Box 9, Item 59918)
- Willis near E. 148th, December 28, 1925 (Box 9, Item 59919)
- 6th Ave & 47th, December 23, 1925 (Box 9, Item 59920)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Blank Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 24, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59921)
- 6th Ave & 47th, February 24, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59922)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 24, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59923)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx), February 24, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59924)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 24, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59925)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 24, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59926)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co. and Van Beuren Co., February 24, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59927)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thomas Cusack Co., February 26, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59928)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59929)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59930)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59931)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59932)
- Willis near E. 148th, February 27, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59933)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 27, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59934)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 27, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59935)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx), April 27, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59936)
- 6th Ave & 47th, April 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59937)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Great Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59938)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by Great Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59939)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by Great Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59940)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59941)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59942)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59943)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59944)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59945)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59946)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Blank Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59947)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Blank Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 25, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59948)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 25, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59949)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 25, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59950)
- 6th Ave & 44th, June 25, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59951)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdor Adv. Co., June 25, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59952)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdor Adv. Co.; view of Bryant Park, June 26, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59953)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdor Adv. Co.; view of Bryant Park, June 26, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59954)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdor Adv. Co., June 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59955)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdor Adv. Co., June 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59956)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdor Adv. Co. and Van Beuren Co., June 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59957)
- Willis near E. 148th, June 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59958)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59959)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by Thomas Cusack. Co., June 29, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59960)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59961)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 29, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59962)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 23, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59963)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 23, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59964)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 23, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59965)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 23, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59966)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 23, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59967)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 23, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59968)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 23, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59969)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; views of Bryant Park, August 26, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59970)
- 6th Ave & 27th Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 26, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59971)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 26, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59972)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 27, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59973)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., August 27, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59974)
- no negative by this number? (Box 9, Item 59975)
- No negative (Box 9, Item 59976)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 27, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59977)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 27, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59978)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59979)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59980)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; view of Bryant Park, October 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59981)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59982)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59983)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1926 (Box 9, Item 59984)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; political cartoon in foreground, October 28, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59985)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59986)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59987)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 28, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59988)
- 6th Ave & 27th Blank billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 29, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59989)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., October 29, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59990)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 21, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59991)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 22, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59992)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 22, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59993)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 21, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59994)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp; political cartoon in foreground, December 22, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59995)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 22, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59996)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 22, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59997)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 22, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59998)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 22, 1926 (Box 10, Item 59999)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 22, 1926 (Box 10, Item 60000)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 22, 1926 (Box 10, Item 60001)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 23, 1926 (Box 10, Item 60002)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 21, 1926 (Box 10, Item 60003)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co.; Drucker & Baltes stamp, December 24, 1926 (Box 10, Item 60004)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 24, 1926 (Box 10, Item 60005)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, February 23, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60006)
- 6th Ave & 27th, February 23, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60007)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60008)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox, February 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60009)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, February 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60010)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60011)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60012)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60013)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60014)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60015)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60016)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60017)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60018)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., February 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60019)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 21, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60020)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 21, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60021)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 21, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60022)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 21, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60023)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 21, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60024)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 21, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60025)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, April 27, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60026)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 27, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60027)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 27, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60028)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60029)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60030)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 29, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60031)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 29, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60032)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., April 28, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60033)
- 6th Ave & 47th Billboards by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 23, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60034)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd, June 23, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60035)
- 6th Ave between 42nd & 43rd Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 23, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60036)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 23, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60037)
- 6th Ave & 44th Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 23, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60038)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 23, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60039)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60040)
- 8th Ave & 110th Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60041)
- 5th Ave & 42nd Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60042)
- 3rd Ave & 166th (Bronx) Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60043)
- Broadway, 47th & 7th Ave Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60044)
- 125th between 7th Ave & Lenox Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 24, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60045)
- 7th Ave & 34th Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60046)
- 6th Ave & 27th Billboard by General Outdoor Adv. Co., June 25, 1927 (Box 10, Item 60047)